Dimineața învăluită în ceață îmi arată o umbră necunoscută
Lângă mine
Distortion of a place in full bloom
The streched out hand writhes and wavers in with the ticks of time
Vrei doar să mă rănești? Îți place să mă privești și să-mi desenezi sentimentele?
Unde este adevărul? Unde îl ții ascuns? Fără niciun fel de regret
In the sky where the wind rushes by
Fly
Glimmer! The voice that woke me up declared loudly
Believe myself!
You have a wish you cannot give up on
Nu uita!
So set loose your one and only impetus
Keep my faith!
To that overprotected smile
Realize!
Cry and shout, that incarnation of weakness that showed its face
Unreavel it with all you've got
Brand new world